(Leonard:)Oh, you heard?
"Scotty, I need more power."
(Leonard:)Sorry. Does Sheldon know
you're sleeping in here?
(Raj:)Are you kidding?
He made me sign a waiver,
(Raj:)participate in
an emergency fire drill
(Raj:)and take a refresher course
in CPR.
(Raj:)Thank God he had a dummy.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
Mouth-to-Mouth Mona.
(Penny:)You know,
she used to date Howard?
Oh, my God, she's that Mona?
(Raj:)Why can't you and my sister
spend your nights here?
(Leonard:)We tried. She doesn't get along
with Sheldon.
(Raj:)Sheldon doesn't get along
(Raj:)It's still no reason
for me to have to listen to you
(Raj:)arm your
photon torpedoes every night.
Okay, well, how about this:
until Priya gets her own place,
(Leonard:)you stay here and I'll stay at
your apartment.
(Raj:)Can I bring girls here?
(Leonard:)You?
(Leonard:)Sure. Bring as many as you want.
(Raj:)Okay, deal.